My name is Michael Moral.
I am 21 years old.
I would like to dance
for the Queen of Britain.
Hello.
What's your name?
I'm Michael.
[BOTH] Michael.
Where are you from?
France.
[BOTH] From France!
Ah, bonjour!.
D'accord, d'accord.
Very good, you're very good.
What will you be doing for us today?
Dancing.
Ah.
I am dancing.
Dancing.
You're a translator?
Yes, translator.
Ah, hello.
Hello.
In France, I watched
Britain's Got Talent on YouTube.
I really hope the judges
give me the chance
to show Britain what I can do.
Do you live here in the UK?
Uh, no.
I live in France.
In France?
So you've came over just
to audition for Britain's Got Talent?
Yes.
[BOTH] Wow.
Welcome.
It's magic.
Oh, yeah.
Ah, great!
[Both] Let's get you on.
Straight on.
Are the pair of you going on? Yeah?
Good luck.
Bonne chance.
That's good luck in French.
Hello.
What are your names?
I'm Michael Moral.
Hi, I'm Claire.
I'm just the translator.
No performance from me.
You're not in the act?
No.
OK.
Where are you from?
I am from France.
We don't need you, it's fine.
I can handle this.
Où habites-tu?
I live in the south of France.
Quel âge as-tu?
I am 20, 21 years old.
Bon.
What are you going to do for us today?
Uh, I'm a dancer.
I'm a dancer.
You're a dancer?
Very, very best of luck Michael,
and the stage is yours.
Bonne chance!
Thank you!
Why do people shave
half of their eyebrow?
Ready?
Yeah.
[PLAYFUL CARNIVAL MUSIC]
[ROBOTIC MACHINE GRINDING]
[SLOW ROCK MUSIC]
[UPLIFTING SYNTHESISER MUSIC]
[UPBEAT ELECTRONIC MUSIC]
[URBAN POP MUSIC]
[MUFFLED EXPLOSION NOISE]
Very good!
[INDISTINCT]
[FRENCH ACCENT] David?
That was probably the best dancing
we've had on the show.
[INAUDIBLE]
If you get voted back,
I can't wait to see
what you're going to do.
It could be a magical show.
Congratulations, terrific.
Thank you.
I agree with David, it was amazing.
I loved that you were so fluid.
Your body looked like
it didn't belong to your head.
Très bien.
Très, très bien.
We'll vote.
David Hasselhoff, is it a yes or a no?
It's a oui!
[INAUDIBLE]
Amanda?
It's a yes from me.
It's 3 yeses, well done!
Congratulations!
["CHAMPION" BY CHIP FT. CHRIS BROWN]
♪ Some people wait their turn,
Some people but not me,
♪ I was born a...
Yeah!
♪ Some people have to fight,
Some people give their life,
Yeah!
Congratulations.
Unbelievable.
Really cool.
Great, he's like the rubber man.
He was absolutely fantastic.
It was great.
♪ I was born a champion.♪